this is the day I've been looking
forward since last December when our
Edition when our previous Edition
finished and I really give you just
happy to see you all here there are many
new faces which is great that means our
community is growing we are going to
have a great time over the next two days
and I hope the experience you will get
out of this conference will influence
the way you create products on a regular
basis so before we get started let me go
through some important informations
about the conference so maybe just an
interaction - to me some Mike and I'll
be your MC for the next two days I'm
also see do at call stack company that
organizes this conference for you and
I'm also doing react native on the core
team in particular are responsible for
releases and some CI stuff so we as a
company quickly jumped on the bandwagon
of react native back in a day and have
been excited by its opportunities since
then I think we were one of the very
first deaf shops to focus on the react
native and to sort of go cross-platform
all in and so we felt like we need to
give back to the community we felt like
we were given this beautiful opportunity
to actually create an even for you so
that you can all meet together that you
can all interact with each other and
learn from each other so for the next
two days hundreds of great developers
from the react native community will be
hanging out here in broad swath and if
someone has suggested this to me a few
years ago I would probably call him
crazy like how is this even possible
that people from all around the world
will be sitting in one place in broad
swath and I will not have to travel
hours to meet my friends so it's the
opportunity that I wish I had myself
when I was starting react and I hope it
will have a positive impact as I said on
you as developers so I wouldn't be
standing here in front of you if it
wasn't for all the awesome companies and
people that believed in our mission and
decided to contribute to the event they
didn't just do it for
recruitment and marketing they did it
because they believe in our community
and they want to make it even better so
please give them a huge round of
applause
all right so react native Europe is a
two-day single track conference it's the
fact that you probably are already aware
of with more than 20 speakers from all
around the world and since react native
can be using variety of ways from
Greenfield to brownfield apps we try to
select lineup in a way that everyone
fund finds satisfied satisfying no
matter the background and what you are
looking in as far as using react native
so we ask that there are no questions
during it or right after the talk best
to reach out the speakers during either
coffee break or after-party if you have
troubles locating them just let
me know or anyone from coastal security
will help you out and you can also
submit a question to our Q&A panel which
I'll tell you we're about in a second
and every once in a while we'll have
coffee breaks as well we know that only
fully hydrated and fed attendees can
enjoy the conference experience at a
hundred percent so we try our best to
prepare a wide range of tasty foods and
drinks just for you so once you grab a
snag and drink coffee it's time to break
the ice right to make things easier we
have prepared special stickers where you
can list topics that the others can ask
you about so it's a great way to lower
the barrier to entry when starting a new
conversation and if you don't have a
sticker yet there are plenty of them at
the registration desk and by the way you
shout out to folks from anything thread
for organizing change we hug and bring
it up this idea I really enjoy it out
and we were more than happy to have it
here as well
[Applause]
it's just a couple of things about the
venue it's kind of bigger than last year
and on the right side is where we are
it's the conference on the opposite side
we'll have the lunch and evening party
chill-out zone and coffee break if you
are tired - feel free to go there and
have some rest and don't worry it has
live streaming inside so we will not
miss any talks unless you really intend
there is you know we all know that there
is no better way to get answers to most
compelling questions than having Q&A and
being able to actually interact with
developers there are building stuff that
you're interested in so we tried our
best to make s comprehensive panel as
possible with representatives from
companies such as Expo Facebook
Playstation and McKinsey & Company it's
going to be perfect opportunity for you
to us anything related to react native
from its performance at a scale and
supporting multiple platforms till its
performance with existing native code
bases and any good comparisons against
other technologies unfortunately
sometimes it can be pretty hard to ask
the question that you really want either
there is a really long queue you are
unsure about your language skills or you
feel like the question was already asked
and remember there are no bad questions
just bad asses so to make it easier for
you we prepared the form in our
conference up where we can submit your
questions to be asked during the panel
it is open till tomorrow mid days so we
got plenty of time to submit whatever
you want based on today and a half of
tomorrow and we will select as many as
possible obviously to fill in the 45
minutes time span we have but if you are
interested about about that topic more
make sure you have our official
conference up on your phone and there
you can find the form to fill it in and
last but not least who doesn't love cool
free stuff right so we have some goodies
waiting for you at a ComStat booth so if
you got some free time during one of the
coffee breaks I just feel free to drop
by and you know we'll sell you all the
details and there is one more thing but
it's the most important thing
as I said this conference purpose is to
create opportunities for people from all
different backgrounds to get various
developers and meet the community in
real life let's keep that in mind and
behave in a way that is respectful to
all members of our conference we will
not tolerate discrimination or
harassment of participants in any form
if you notice any violations of our code
of conduct please report them directly
to either me call stager security staff
will examine them all and action will be
taken immediately full version of our
official conference of full version of
our code of conduct can be found on the
website Conference Code of Conduct calm
you can see the link it's it's it's
colored red on the slide alright that's
about everything you need to know to get
started so who's ready for reactive
Europe
[Applause]